<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Iwen Su</title>
    <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Iwen Su</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Healthy Oceans Tech and Finance Forum</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/scoot-adb-forum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/scoot-adb-forum/</guid>
      <description>Scene setter, “Financing Sustainable Aquaculture,” Asian Development Bank Healthy Oceans Tech and Finance Forum 2022, January 2022.
Set the scene for a spotlight panel discussion between investors, aquaculture companies and feed companies.
Description of the 2022 Healthy Oceans Tech and Finance Forum here.
Blue Foods, Financing Sustainable Aquaculture Session Panel Participants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafood Source Webinar</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/scoot-seafoodsource/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/scoot-seafoodsource/</guid>
      <description>Panelist, “Forecasting Ocean Weather | The solution to protect, insure, &amp;amp; invest in salmon aquaculture,” SeafoodSource Webinar, January 2022.
As Senior Data Scientist at Scoot Science, talked about our proposed framework for tracking carbon footprint for the global salmon industry. The panel included myself, our CEO, CIO and Business Development Specialist.
PRESENTATION OVERVIEW:
Extreme ocean events have threatened salmon health at aquaculture sites globally for decades. Now, with the help of Scoot Science, many ocean events that cause fish mortalities are predictable and insurable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish Oil: Who is it for?</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/fishful_future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/fishful_future/</guid>
      <description>Guest blog contributor to Fishful Future, a collaborative initiative funded by the NOAA Saltonstall-Kennedy Grant Program to move towards a zero waste seafood industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Design &amp; Content Editor</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/cosap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/cosap/</guid>
      <description>Finalized content, improved layout and organization for Offshore Mussel Farming pages, added relevant resources, and created subscriber functionality for COSAP website.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Data Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/ca-aqua-dash/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/ca-aqua-dash/</guid>
      <description>Created a CA Aquaculture Dashboard for synthesizing and visualizing existing data from a variety of sources, including US Department of Agriculture and NOAA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ocean Health Index Guest Blog</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/ohi-mariculture-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/ohi-mariculture-blog/</guid>
      <description>Read my guest blog post, &amp;ldquo;Fellowship Feature: Expanding mariculture&amp;rdquo;, on the Ocean Health Index project page!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NCEAS Roundtable Series</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/ohi-fellows-roundtable/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/ohi-fellows-roundtable/</guid>
      <description>Presenter, &amp;ldquo;Ocean Health Index Global Fellows Program Seminar&amp;rdquo;, NCEAS Roundtable Series, Santa Barbara, September 2018.
Presented on the Ocean Health Index (OHI) Global Assessment framework, the open data science tools used in evaluating ocean health, the value of the fellowship program, and the data exploration dashboard I created for the OHI Mariculture goal.
PRESENTATION OVERVIEW:
The Ocean Health Index (OHI) Global Fellows Program is training the next generation of ocean data scientists through global ocean health assessments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ocean Health Index</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/ohi-global/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/ohi-global/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Calculated status of fisheries, mariculture, MPAs, and social progress for the 2018 OHI Global Assessment at NCEAS. Synthesized large datasets, communicated research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Data Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/ohi-dash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/ohi-dash/</guid>
      <description>The Data Exploration Dashboard I created for the OHI Project provides a quick glance into the data behind calculating global scores. Read about it in my featured article!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Conversation about Aquaculture</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/a-conversation-about-aquaculture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/a-conversation-about-aquaculture/</guid>
      <description>Organizer, “A Conversation about Aquaculture”, student-led presentation series featuring local academic and industry experts in aquaculture, Bren School, Santa Barbara, June 2018.
Helped secure funding from various sources, outlined and monitored event budget, coordinated with guest speakers before, during, and after the event, and managed programming logistics.
EVENT OVERVIEW
Aquaculture is a fascinating industry that intersects with many different fields that we study here at Bren. We want to hold a ‘Night of Aquaculture’ to allow participants to explore a range of topics, discuss current industry direction and development, and to have the opportunity to connect with people based in California doing important work in the aquaculture space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seaweed Aquaculture in Southern California</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/seaweed-aquaculture-in-southern-california/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/seaweed-aquaculture-in-southern-california/</guid>
      <description>Investigated the feasibility of seaweed aquaculture in southern California for Santa Barbara Mariculture and the Sustainable Aquaculture Research Center.
Presenter, “Testing the Economic Feasibility of Seaweed Aquaculture in Southern California,” Master Project Defenses, Bren School, Santa Barbara, March 2018.
Presented project scope and results to an academic panel. Presentations were open to the public.
PRESENTATION OVERVIEW:
Globally, aquaculture systems produce 23.8 million tonnes of seaweed, worth $6.4 billion USD annually. The majority of edible seaweeds consumed in California is imported from Asia and any local seaweed product is overwhelmingly sourced from wild harvesters in Northern California.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fishery Decision Support Tool</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/tnc-cgc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/tnc-cgc/</guid>
      <description>Streamlined marine spatial planning for the CA Groundfish Collective and TNC by implementing SeaSketch as a cloud-based, planning tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VSE Mussel Farming Site Selection Workshop</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/vse-mussel-farming-lease/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/vse-mussel-farming-lease/</guid>
      <description>Invited workshop participant, “Gathering Community Input on the Location of VSE Mussel Farming Lease Sites”, Ventura Shellfish Enterprise Site Selection Workshop, Ventura Harbor, July 2017.
Represented SeaSketch at the site selection workshop and collected public comments.
WORKSHOP OVERVIEW:
The Ventura Shellfish Enterprise (VSE) held a series of site selection workshops from July to August 2017. These collaborative and interactive workshops are aimed at gathering information from stakeholders to help evaluate and identify potential locations for mussel farming plots within a larger candidate growing area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafood Traceability Forum</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/seafood-traceability-forum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/portfolio/seafood-traceability-forum/</guid>
      <description>Invited workshop participant, LMU-UCLA Seafood Traceability Forum, Loyola Marymount University, Los Angeles, April 2017.
Participated in forum breakout sessions to discuss various seafood traceability issues.
WORKSHOP OVERVIEW:
Developed in collaboration with scientists from LMU, UCLA, and various regulatory agencies, this forum will be an open discussion on the current state of seafood traceability in the Greater Los Angeles area, and will explore options for addressing the problem of seafood mislabeling.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
